Finding Aid for Jacob Ellsworth Reighard Papers 1887-1942
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Jacob Ellsworth Reighard Papers 1887-1942 1890-1920
Reighard, Jacob Ellsworth, 1861-1942.
The Jacob Ellsworth Reighard collection contains the papers and photographs of a noted professor of zoology, including his research, class lectures and correspondence. Jacob Reighard was responsible for the development of modern zoological teaching and research at the University of Michigan and a national leader in the field of zoology.
86457 A-2
13 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The collection was donated by the University of Michigan Department of Zoology (donor no. 21009 ) in 1945.
The collection is open for research.
Jacob Ellsworth Reighard, professor of zoology at the University of Michigan, was born at LaPorte, Indiana, July 2, 1861, the son of John D. and Mary Hulburt Reighard. Reighard attended the public schools at LaPorte, Indiana, entered the Literary Department of the University of Michigan in the fall of 1878, and graduated with the Ph.D degree in 1882. Following his graduation he taught for three years in Indiana and Massachusetts. During the last two years of this period he was a private student of Dr. E.L. Mark of Harvard University. After this he spent a year at Michigan in the study of medicine.
He began his teaching career at Michigan in 1886 when he was appointed Instructor in Zoology. During the absence of Professor Joseph B. Steere he served as Acting Assistant Professor, 1887-88, and was made Assistant Professor of Zoology in 1889. Jacob Reighard was directly responsible for many changes in the character of zoology courses. To the old group of courses dealing with the systematics and natural history of various animal groups, he added Vertebrate Dissections, Histology of Vertebrates, Elements of Biology (Animal Life), and Embryology, each of which required laboratory work as well as the usual lectures or recitations. Beginning in 1889 the zoological courses were listed in two groups in the catalogue, "General Zoology" Systematic taught by Professor Steere, and Animal Morphology given by Professor Reighard. In 1892 Professor Reighard was made Professor of Animal Morphology; his department was separated from the old department and was known as the Morphological Laboratory.
Professor Reighard spent the year 1894-95 in study at the University of Freiburg, Germany. After his return in 1895 his title was changed to Professor of Zoology and Director of the Zoological Laboratory and the Museum of Zoology. The museum position he retained until 1913. He continued as Director of the Zoological Laboratory until 1925 when he relinquished the active directorship, retaining his professorship until his retirement as professor emeritus in 1927. In 1936, after the close of his active career, the University of Michigan conferred upon him the honorary degree of Doctor of Science.
With Professor Frederick C. Newcombe and Dr. George P. Burns of the Department of Botany, Professor Reighard was a cofounder of the University of Michigan Biological Station on Douglas Lake in Cheboygan County in 1909 and was its first Director. Professor Reighard's contribution to the development of the research function of the Museum of Zoology during his directorship, 1895-1913, was stated thus by his successor: "During this time the museum was made up of a number of collections under the direction of the heads of several teaching departments. It is largely due to Professor Reighard that the Museum of Zoology did not become an adjunct to a teaching department but was an independent research department of the University. Professor Reighard directed the scientific work of the Michigan Fish Commission for the years 1890-1895 during which time a number of important research projects were carried through to completion. Although for lack of support this series of investigations came to a close in 1895, the present Institute for Fisheries Research of the Michigan Department of Conservation probably should be considered to be "the delayed outgrowth of the scientific work which he did for the Michigan Fish Commission" some decades earlier.
For the years 1898-1901. Professor Reighard was in charge of the Biological Survey of the Great Lakes conducted by the U.S. Fish Commission, and for some years beginning in 1917 he directed important researches on the food fishes of the Great Lakes. As an outgrowth of the latter and possibly indirectly as the result of his own earlier work on the Great Lakes came the establishment in Ann Arbor of the Great Lakes Laboratory of the U.S. Bureau of Fisheries (now the U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service).
Professor Reighard held membership and served as officer in various scientific organizations including A.A.A.S. (vice president of Section F, 1910), American Society of Naturalists, American Society of Zoologists (vice president of the eastern branch and president of the central branch in 1903), the Ecological Society of America, American Fisheries Society (president, 1915), and the Michigan Academy of Science (president, 1900). He presided at two sessions on Animal Behavior at the International Zoological Congress at Boston in 1907. For some years he served as trustee and member of the Executive Committee of the Marine Biological Laboratory, Woods Hole, and was a member of the Board of Scientific Advisers of the Michigan Geological and Biological Survey.
Professor Reighard was always interested in the improvement of methods and in the application of new methods to zoological research. An expert photographer, he described methods of photographing embryos, of photographing breeding fishes in their natural habitats, and of photographing coral-reef fishes by means of a submerged camera which he devised. His book on the "Anatomy of the Cat" written with H.S. Jennings has had extensive use in anatomical laboratories and was revised by Dr. Rush Elliott in the 1930's with the collaboration of Professor Reighard.
In the later years of his active career, increasing deafness caused Reighard to learn speech reading. His interest in helping others, afflicted with the same infirmity, led him to translate a number of German papers on this subject and to prepare several original papers, some of which are still in manuscript form. This work and the completion of manuscripts on breeding habits of fishes occupied much of his time after his retirement.
Jacob Reighard was responsible for the development of modern zoological teaching and research at the University of Michigan. Through his teaching, his researches and his leadership in zoological organizations he exerted a marked influence upon zoology in the United States. Reighard died February 13, 1942 in Ann Arbor, Michigan. [This sketch is an edited version of the memorial read before the Faculty Meeting, College of Literature, Science, and the Arts, April 6, 1942, and was compiled by George R. La Rue, Peter Okkelberg, and John F. Shepard.]
The Jacob Reighard collection consists of thirteen feet of correspondence, speeches, lectures, drafts of writings, University of Michigan lecture and course materials, and files of research materials and field notes. The collection covers the period of 1887 to 1942. The collection has been organized into four series; Correspondence, Writings and Speeches, University Lecture and Course Materials, and Research Materials and Field Notes. This finding aid also contains a selective inventory of correspondents found within the Reighard papers.
Subjects:
Deaf--Means of communication.; Death.; Evolution.; Fishes--Great Lakes.; Fur trade--Michigan.; Great Lakes.; Lombard, Warren P. (Warren Plimpton), 1855-1939.; Manistee River (Mich.); Michigan. State Board of Fish Commissioners.; Philippines--History--1898-1946.; Underwater photography.; Reighard, Jacob Ellsworth, 1861-1942.; United States Fish Commission.; University of Michigan. Biological Station.; University of Michigan. Dept. of Zoology.; University of Michigan--Faculty.; University of Michigan. Museum of Zoology.; University of Michigan. Zoological Laboratory.; Zoology.; World War, 1914-1918--Education and the war.; World War, 1914-1918--Michigan--Ann Arbor.
Subjects - Visual Material:
Fish.; Laboratories.; Zoology.
Contributors:
Abel, John Jacob, 1857-1938.; Adams, Charles C. (Charles Christopher), 1873-1955.; Agassiz, Alexander, 1835-1910.; Amateur Fencers League of America.; Angell, James Burrill, 1829-1916.; Bailey, L. H. (Liberty Hyde), 1858-1954.; Baker, Frank Collins, 1867-1942.; Barbour, Levi L. (Levi Lewis), 1840-1925.; Birge, E. A. (Edward Asahel), 1851-1950.; Bumpus, Hermon Carey, 1862-1943.; Burrows, Julius C. (Julius Caesar), 1837-1915.; Cattell, James McKeen, 1860-1944.; Clark, Hubert Lyman, 1870-1947.; Clements, William L. (William Lawrence), 1861-1934.; Cobb, Frank Irving, 1869-1923.; Conklin, Edward Grant, 1863-1952.; Davenport, Charles Benedict, 1866-1944.; Dean, Bashford, 1867-1928.; Dewey, John, 1859-1952.; Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1844-1930.; Fordney, Joseph W. (Joseph Warren), 1853-1932.; Gage, Simon Henry, 1851-1944.; Gilman, Daniel Coit, 1831-1908.; Harvey, E. Newton (Edmund Newton), 1887-1959.; Hay, Oliver Perry, 1846-1930.; Herrick, Francis Hobart, 1858-1940.; Hubbard, Lucius L. (Lucius Lee), 1849-1933.; Hubbs, Carl L. (Carl Leavitt), 1894-1979.; Hutchins, Harry B. (Harry Burns), 1847-1930.; Jenks, Jeremiah Whipple, 1856-1929.; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947.; Johnston, John Black, 1868-1939.; Jordan, David Starr, 1851-1931.; Kellogg, John Harvey, 1852-1943.; Lane, Alfred C. (Alfred Church), b. 1863.; Langley, S. P. (Samuel Pierpont), 1834-1906.; Larue, George R. (George Roger), b. 1882.; Lillie, Frank Rattray, 1870-1947.; Loeb, Jacques, 1859-1924.; McMillan, James, 1838-1902.; Mark, E. L. (Edward Laurens), b. 1847.; Meyer, Adolf, 1866-1950.; Morgan, Thomas Hunt, 1866-1945.; Mosher, Eliza Maria, 1846-1928.; National Conference on Race Betterment.; Okkelberg, Peter Olaus, 1880-; Osborn, Henry Fairfield, 1857-1935.; Peabody, George Foster, 1852-1938.; Pearl, Raymond, 1879-1940.; Pingree, Hazen S., 1840-1901.; Putnam, Frederic Ward, 1839-1915.; Ruthven, Alexander Grant, 1882-1971.; Shull, Aaron Franklin, 1881-1961.; Smith, William Alden, 1859-1932.; Stockard, Charles Rupert, 1879-1939.; Wenley, R. M. (Robert Mark), 1861-1929.; Whitman, Charles Otis, 1842-1910.; Woodward, Robert Simpson, 1849-1924.; Worcester, Dean C. (Dean Conant), 1866-1924.
Genre/Form:
Photographs.; Underwater photography.; Watercolor paintings.
- Biographical material
  - Biographical material (Box 1)
- Bibliographies of writings
  - Bibliographies of writings (Box 1)
- Correspondence
  The Correspondence series (boxes 1-8) are especially complete for the years 1890 to 1920, the period of Reighard's greatest professional accomplishment. Thereafter the correspondence dwindles to a few folders. The letters are rich in discussion of the development of zoology as a profession, in Reighard's studies of Great Lakes fish biology, in his administration of the University's zoological Laboratory, its biological station at Douglas Lake, and the Museum of Zoology in Ann Arbor. Reighard was teacher and colleague to America's most important zoologists, whose papers are represented in these correspondence files. H.S. Jennings, noted for his work in animal behavior and genetics at Johns Hopkins University, worked closely with Reighard at the University and at Douglas Lake. Dean C. Worcester, member of the first U.S. Philippine Commission, wrote long and extensive letters describing his life in the Far East. A more complete listing of Reighard's correspondents is included with this finding aid.
  Largely a zoological collection, the Reighard correspondence also describes such subject areas as the impact of the First World War on the University of Michigan, the dispute among faculty members over an allegedly pro-German teacher (Walter Kcelz), the attempt to legislate the fur seal trade (April 1913), the development of underwater photography (letter from Francis N. Balch, July 1, 1910), and the problems and adjustments of Reighard as a hearing-impaired individual.
  - 1890-1899
    - 1890-1891 (Box 1)
    - 1892 (Box 1)
    - January-June 1893 (Box 1)
    - July-December 1893 (Box 1)
    - January 1894 (Box 1)
    - February 1894 (Box 1)
    - March 1894 (Box 1)
    - April-June 1894 (Box 1)
    - July-September 1894 (Box 1)
    - October-December 1894 (Box 1)
    - January-February 1895 (Box 1)
    - March-June 1895 (Box 1)
    - July-August 1895 (Box 1)
    - September-October 1895 (Box 1)
    - November 1895 (Box 1)
    - December 1895 (Box 1)
    - January 1896 (Box 1)
    - February 1896 (Box 1)
    - March 1896 (Box 1)
    - April 1896 (Box 1)
    - May 1896 (Box 1)
    - June 1896 (Box 1)
    - July-August 1896 (Box 1)
    - September-October 1896 (Box 1)
    - November-December 1896 (Box 1)
    - January 1897 (Box 1)
    - February 1897 (Box 1)
    - March 1897 (Box 1)
    - April 1897 (Box 1)
    - May 1897 (Box 1)
    - June-July 1897 (Box 1)
    - August 1897 (Box 1)
    - September 1897 (Box 1)
    - October 1897 (Box 1)
    - November 1897 (Box 1)
    - December 1897 (Box 1)
    - January 1898 (Box 1)
    - February 1898 (Box 1)
    - March 1898 (Box 1)
    - April 1898 (Box 1)
    - May 1898 (Box 1)
    - June 1-12, 1898 (Box 1)
    - June 13-20, 1898 (Box 1)
    - June 21-30, 1898 (Box 1)
    - July 1-15, 1898 (Box 1)
    - July 16-31, 1898 (Box 1)
    - August 1-10, 1898 (Box 1)
    - August 11-20, 1898 (Box 1)
    - August 21-31, 1898 (Box 1)
    - September 1898 (Box 1)
    - October 1898 (Box 1)
    - November 1-15, 1898 (Box 1)
    - November 16-30, 1898 (Box 1)
    - December 1-15, 1898 (Box 1)
    - December 16-31, 1898 (Box 1)
    - January 1-10, 1899 (Box 1)
    - January 11-25, 1899 (Box 1)
    - January 26-31, 1899 (Box 1)
    - February 1-15, 1899 (Box 2)
    - February 16-20, 1899 (Box 2)
    - February 21-28, 1899 (Box 2)
    - March 1-10, 1899 (Box 2)
    - March 11-20, 1899 (Box 2)
    - March 21-31, 1899 (Box 2)
    - April 1-15, 1899 (Box 2)
    - April 16-30, 1899 (Box 2)
    - May 1-10, 1899 (Box 2)
    - May 11-20, 1899 (Box 2)
    - May 21-31, 1899 (Box 2)
    - June 1-10, 1899 (Box 2)
    - June 11-20, 1899 (Box 2)
    - June 21-25, 1899 (Box 2)
    - June 26-30, 1899 (Box 2)
    - July 1-10, 1899 (Box 2)
    - July 11-15, 1899 (Box 2)
    - July 16-20, 1899 (Box 2)
    - July 21-25, 1899 (Box 2)
    - July 26-31, 1899 (Box 2)
    - August 1-10, 1899 (Box 2)
    - August 11-20, 1899 (Box 2)
    - August 21-31, 1899 (Box 2)
    - September 1-15, 1899 (Box 2)
    - September 16-30, 1899 (Box 2)
    - October 1-15, 1899 (Box 2)
    - October 16-31, 1899 (Box 2)
    - November 1-15, 1899 (Box 2)
    - November 16-30, 1899 (Box 2)
    - December 1-15, 1899 (Box 2)
    - December 16-31, 1899 (Box 2)
  - 1900-1909
    - January 1-15, 1900 (Box 2)
    - January 16-31, 1900 (Box 2)
    - February 1900 (Box 2)
    - March 1-15, 1900 (Box 2)
    - March 16-31, 1900 (Box 2)
    - April 1900 (Box 2)
    - May 1-15, 1900 (Box 2)
    - May 16-31, 1900 (Box 2)
    - June 1-10, 1900 (Box 2)
    - June 11-20, 1900 (Box 2)
    - June 21-30, 1900 (Box 2)
    - July 1-10, 1900 (Box 2)
    - July 11-20, 1900 (Box 2)
    - July 21-31, 1900 (Box 2)
    - August 1-10, 1900 (Box 2)
    - August 11-31, 1900 (Box 2)
    - September 1900 (Box 2)
    - October 1-10, 1900 (Box 2)
    - October 11-31, 1900 (Box 2)
    - November 1900 (Box 3)
    - December 1900 (Box 3)
    - January 1-15, 1901 (Box 3)
    - January 16-31, 1901 (Box 3)
    - February 1901 (Box 3)
    - March 1901 (Box 3)
    - April 1-15, 1901 (Box 3)
    - April 16-25, 1901 (Box 3)
    - April 26-30, 1901 (Box 3)
    - May 1-10, 1901 (Box 3)
    - May 11-15, 1901 (Box 3)
    - May 16-20, 1901 (Box 3)
    - May 21-25, 1901 (Box 3)
    - May 26-31, 1901 (Box 3)
    - June 1-10, 1901 (Box 3)
    - June 11-20, 1901 (Box 3)
    - June 21-30, 1901 (Box 3)
    - July 1-5, 1901 (Box 3)
    - July 6-10, 1901 (Box 3)
    - July 11-15, 1901 (Box 3)
    - July 16-20, 1901 (Box 3)
    - July 21-25, 1901 (Box 3)
    - July 26-31, 1901 (Box 3)
    - August 1-5, 1901 (Box 3)
    - August 6-10, 1901 (Box 3)
    - August 11-20, 1901 (Box 3)
    - August 21-31, 1901 (Box 3)
    - September 1-15, 1901 (Box 3)
    - September 16-30, 1901 (Box 3)
    - October 1-15, 1901 (Box 3)
    - October 16-31, 1901 (Box 3)
    - November 1-15, 1901 (Box 3)
    - November 16-30, 1901 (Box 3)
    - December 1-15, 1901 (Box 3)
    - December 16-31, 1901 (Box 3)
    - 1901 undated (Box 3)
    - January 1902 (Box 3)
    - February 1902 (Box 3)
    - March 1902 (Box 3)
    - April 1902 (Box 3)
    - May 1902 (Box 3)
    - June 1-10, 1902 (Box 3)
    - June 11-30, 1902 (Box 3)
    - July 1-15, 1902 (Box 3)
    - July 16-31, 1902 (Box 3)
    - August 1-15, 1902 (Box 3)
    - August 16-31, 1902 (Box 3)
    - September 1902 (Box 4)
    - October 1902 (Box 4)
    - November 1902 (Box 4)
    - December 1902 (Box 4)
    - January 1-11, 1903 (Box 4)
    - January 12-19, 1903 (Box 4)
    - January 20-31, 1903 (Box 4)
    - February 1-15, 1903 (Box 4)
    - February 16-28, 1903 (Box 4)
    - March 1-19, 1903 (Box 4)
    - March 20-31, 1903 (Box 4)
    - April 1-7, 1903 (Box 4)
    - April 8-21, 1903 (Box 4)
    - April 22-30, 1903 (Box 4)
    - May 1-14, 1903 (Box 4)
    - May 15-23, 1903 (Box 4)
    - May 24-31, 1903 (Box 4)
    - June 1-10, 1903 (Box 4)
    - June 11-21, 1903 (Box 4)
    - June 22-30, 1903 (Box 4)
    - July 1-17, 1903 (Box 4)
    - July 18-31, 1903 (Box 4)
    - August 1903 (Box 4)
    - September 1903 (Box 4)
    - October 1903 (Box 4)
    - November 1903 (Box 4)
    - December 1-11, 1903 (Box 4)
    - December 12-31, 1903 (Box 4)
    - January 1904 (Box 4)
    - February 1904 (Box 4)
    - March 1904 (Box 4)
    - April 1904 (Box 4)
    - May 1904 (Box 4)
    - June 1-18, 1904 (Box 4)
    - June 19-30, 1904 (Box 4)
    - July 1904 (Box 4)
    - August 1904 (Box 4)
    - September-October 1904 (Box 4)
    - November 1904 (Box 4)
    - December 1904 (Box 4)
    - January-February 1905 (Box 4)
    - March 1905 (Box 4)
    - April 1-15, 1905 (Box 4)
    - April 16-22, 1905 (Box 4)
    - April 23-30, 1905 (Box 4)
    - May 1-10, 1905 (Box 4)
    - May 11-31, 1905 (Box 4)
    - June 1-9, 1905 (Box 4)
    - June 10-30, 1905 (Box 4)
    - July 1905 (Box 4)
    - August 1905 (Box 4)
    - September 1905 (Box 4)
    - October 1905 (Box 4)
    - November 1905 (Box 4)
    - December 1905 (Box 4)
    - January 1906 (Box 5)
    - February 1906 (Box 5)
    - March 1-2, 1906 (Box 5)
    - March 13-31, 1906 (Box 5)
    - April 1-15, 1906 (Box 5)
    - April 16-30, 1906 (Box 5)
    - May 1-15, 1906 (Box 5)
    - May 16-31, 1906 (Box 5)
    - June 1-20, 1906 (Box 5)
    - June 21-30, 1906 (Box 5)
    - July 1-20, 1906 (Box 5)
    - July 21-31, 1906 (Box 5)
    - August 1-15, 1906 (Box 5)
    - August 16-31, 1906 (Box 5)
    - September 1-18, 1906 (Box 5)
    - September 19-30, 1906 (Box 5)
    - October 1906 (Box 5)
    - November 1906 (Box 5)
    - December 1906 (Box 5)
    - January 1907 (Box 5)
    - February 1907 (Box 5)
    - March 1-13, 1907 (Box 5)
    - March 14-31, 1907 (Box 5)
    - April 1907 (Box 5)
    - May 1907 (Box 5)
    - June 1907 (Box 5)
    - July 1907 (Box 5)
    - August 1907 (Box 5)
    - September 1907 (Box 5)
    - October 1907 (Box 5)
    - November 1907 (Box 5)
    - December 1907 (Box 5)
    - 1907 undated (Box 5)
    - January 1908 (Box 5)
    - February 1908 (Box 5)
    - March 1-15, 1908 (Box 5)
    - March 16-31, 1908 (Box 5)
    - April 1-16, 1908 (Box 5)
    - April 17-30, 1908 (Box 5)
    - May 1-18, 1908 (Box 5)
    - May 19-31, 1908 (Box 5)
    - June 1-15, 1908 (Box 5)
    - June 16-30, 1908 (Box 5)
    - July 1-11, 1908 (Box 5)
    - July 12-21, 1908 (Box 5)
    - July 22-31, 1908 (Box 5)
    - August 1-17, 1908 (Box 5)
    - August 18-31, 1908 (Box 5)
    - September 1-18, 1908 (Box 5)
    - September 19-30, 1908 (Box 5)
    - October 1908 (Box 5)
    - November 1-15, 1908 (Box 5)
    - November 16-30, 1908 (Box 5)
    - December 1-14, 1908 (Box 5)
    - December 15-31, 1908 (Box 5)
    - January 1-18, 1909 (Box 5)
    - January 19-31, 1909 (Box 5)
    - February 1-10, 1909 (Box 5)
    - February 11-28, 1909 (Box 5)
    - March 1-22, 1909 (Box 5)
    - March 23-31, 1909 (Box 5)
    - April 1-18, 1909 (Box 6)
    - April 19-30, 1909 (Box 6)
    - May 1909 (Box 6)
    - June 1-7, 1909 (Box 6)
    - June 8-16, 1909 (Box 6)
    - June 17-30, 1909 (Box 6)
    - July 1-2, 1909 (Box 6)
    - July 3-12, 1909 (Box 6)
    - July 13-21, 1909 (Box 6)
    - July 22-31, 1909 (Box 6)
    - August 1909 (Box 6)
    - September 1909 (Box 6)
    - October 1909 (Box 6)
    - November 1909 (Box 6)
    - December 1-7, 1909 (Box 6)
    - December 8-31, 1909 (Box 6)
  - 1910-1919
    - January 1910 (Box 6)
    - February 1910 (Box 6)
    - March 1910 (Box 6)
    - April 1910 (Box 6)
    - May 1910 (Box 6)
    - June 1910 (Box 6)
    - July 1-20, 1910 (Box 6)
    - July 21-31, 1910 (Box 6)
    - August 1910 (Box 6)
    - September 1910 (Box 6)
    - October 1910 (Box 6)
    - November 1910 (Box 6)
    - December 1910 (Box 6)
    - 1910 undated (Box 6)
    - January 1911 (Box 6)
    - February 1911 (Box 6)
    - March 1911 (Box 6)
    - April 1-20, 1911 (Box 6)
    - April 21-30, 1911 (Box 6)
    - May 1-10, 1911 (Box 6)
    - May 11-20, 1911 (Box 6)
    - May 21-31, 1911 (Box 6)
    - June 1911 (Box 6)
    - July 1911 (Box 6)
    - August 1911 (Box 6)
    - September 1-10, 1911 (Box 6)
    - September 11-30, 1911 (Box 6)
    - October 1911 (Box 6)
    - November 1-15, 1911 (Box 6)
    - November 16-30, 1911 (Box 6)
    - December 1911 (Box 6)
    - January 1-20, 1912 (Box 6)
    - January 21-31, 1912 (Box 6)
    - February 1912 (Box 6)
    - March 1-20, 1912 (Box 6)
    - March 21-31, 1912 (Box 6)
    - April 1-15, 1912 (Box 6)
    - April 16-30, 1912 (Box 6)
    - May-June 1912 (Box 6)
    - July 1912 (Box 7)
    - August 1912 (Box 7)
    - September-October 1912 (Box 7)
    - November-December 1912 (Box 7)
    - 1912 undated (Box 7)
    - January 1913 (Box 7)
    - February 1913 (Box 7)
    - March 1913 (Box 7)
    - April 1913 (Box 7)
    - May 1-15, 1913 (Box 7)
    - May 16-31, 1913 (Box 7)
    - June 1913 (Box 7)
    - July 1-15, 1913 (Box 7)
    - July 16-31, 1913 (Box 7)
    - August 1913 (Box 7)
    - September-October 1913 (Box 7)
    - November-December 1913 (Box 7)
    - January 1914 (Box 7)
    - February 1914 (Box 7)
    - March 1914 (Box 7)
    - April 1914 (Box 7)
    - May-June 1914 (Box 7)
    - July-August 1914 (Box 7)
    - September-December 1914 (Box 7)
    - 1914 undated (Box 7)
    - January-February 1915 (Box 7)
    - March-April 1915 (Box 7)
    - May 1915 (Box 7)
    - June 1915 (Box 7)
    - July-August 1915 (Box 7)
    - September 1915 (Box 7)
    - October 1915 (Box 7)
    - November-December 1915 (Box 7)
    - 1915 undated (Box 7)
    - January 1916 (Box 7)
    - February 1916 (Box 7)
    - March-April 1916 (Box 7)
    - May 1916 (Box 7)
    - June 1916 (Box 7)
    - July 1916 (Box 7)
    - August 1916 (Box 7)
    - September 1916 (Box 7)
    - October 1916 (Box 7)
    - November 1916 (Box 7)
    - December 1916 (Box 7)
    - January 1917 (Box 7)
    - February 1917 (Box 7)
    - March 1917 (Box 7)
    - April 1917 (Box 7)
    - May 1917 (Box 7)
    - June 1917 (Box 7)
    - July 1917 (Box 7)
    - August 1917 (Box 7)
    - September 1917 (Box 7)
    - October 1917 (Box 7)
    - November 1917 (Box 7)
    - April -December, 1934 (Box 7)
    - January 1918 (Box 8)
    - February 1918 (Box 8)
    - March 1918 (Box 8)
    - April 1918 (Box 8)
    - May 1918 (Box 8)
    - June 1918 (Box 8)
    - July 1918 (Box 8)
    - August 1918 (Box 8)
    - September 1918 (Box 8)
    - October 1918 (Box 8)
    - November 1918 (Box 8)